https://goldnwax.com/privacy-statement

Last added items
Subtotal:
$0.00
View cart
Checkout
The order subtotal is less than the minimum allowed value ($1.00)
Privacy Statement
You can shop at www.goldnwax.com with confidence. We have partnered with Authorize.Net, a leading payment gateway since 1996, to accept credit cards and electronic check payments safely and securely for our customers.The Authorize.Net Payment Gateway manages the complex routing of sensitive customer information through the electronic check and credit card processing networks. See an online payments diagram  to see how it works.The company adheres to strict industry standards for payment processing, including:128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology for secure Internet Protocol (IP) transactions.  Industry leading encryption hardware and software methods and security protocols to protect customer information. Compliance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS).For additional information regarding the privacy of your sensitive cardholder data, please read the Authorize.Net Privacy Policy .www.goldnwax.com  is registered with the Authorize.Net Verified Merchant Seal program.
Payment Processing The Types of Information We Collect And How We Use It:IP Addresses:We use IP Addresses for statistical and system administration purposes. IP addresses are anonymously logged to track a users session. We do not link IP addresses with any personally identifiable information. This means that a users session will be logged but that user will remain anonymous to us. We can and will us IP address to identify a user when necessary to enforce our terms of service or protect our site, network, advertisers or users. The only exception to this is when a user places an order. At that time, the session id and/or IP address of the user will be logged. This information is retained for use in instances of fraud to assist in identifying the perpetrators.Cookies:We use session cookies to enhance the performance of certain services within our site. This cookie does not contain any personally identifiable information about usersContact Information:We collect contact information (name, address, telephone number, email address and URL) through various registration forms and through the ordering process. This information is used to provide you with services that you requested, contact you when necessary, and/or to send you additional information regarding goldnwax.com.Financial Information:We collect certain financial information (credit card information) from users who order services from us. This information is used solely to bill for services that you order. This information is not retained on our web servers and is not transmitted over the Internet unless encrypted.With Whom Do We Share Information:goldnwax.com will not sell, share or rent your personally identifiable information with  anyone.Choice / Opt-Out Of Promotional and Marketing Communications:If you no longer wish to receive our occasional newsletters or other marketing communications from goldnwax.com you may opt-out of receiving these by following the unsubscribe / removal instructions located at the very bottom of these communications or by sending an email to us from our Contact Us page.SECURITYgoldnwax.com uses secure servers to protect your personal information, including your name, address, and credit card information. Ours secure server protects all pages using state of the art Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption. We also use the latest firewall technology to ensure your information remains secure. Secure pages will be indicated in most browsers by a lock icon the window. Gold n Wax website is a starfield secure site, please click here to view the certificateData Security / Data Access:Whenever we need to collect sensitive personal information such as credit card information that information will be encrypted and protected with the current standard (or better) in encryption technology, currently Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). While on a secure page information that you provide, such as your name or credit-card number, is encrypted so that other people can not read it.Our organization is committed to fighting online fraud and to instituting fraud prevention policies, including:* Ensuring that all credit card information is encrypted and/or password-protected.* Maintaining data transmissions in a secure environment with limited, authorized access.* Monitoring behavior and activities of employees and deploying a rigorous auditing process.* Keeping all security software up-to-date and firewalls properly configured.* Sufficiently logging all Internet traffic.* Monitoring site on a regular basis (at least daily).* Ensuring that business databases are not directly connected to the Web.* Contacting law enforcement in any situation where crime is suspected.How To Contact Us:If you have any questions about the goldnwax.com privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with us please email using email address from our Contact Us page.
Sign up for G n W Designs Inc news
Email
*
Subscribe
Can't subscribe you right now. Try later
Thank you for subscribing to the newsletter! We hope you enjoy shopping at G n W Designs Inc
© 2007 - 2020 G n W Designs Inc. All rights reserved.
Powered by X-Cart
